hybrid
гибриде
welcome here please tell me
приветствую вот скажите пожалуйста я
I am conducting a sociological study
провожу социологическое исследование
what is the percentage of idiots in russia please tell me
какой в россии процент идиотов скажите
if you support the war in ukraine
пожалуйста вы поддержите войну в украине
or not
или нет
here I am once portfolio graph okay
вот сюда меня раз портфолио граф окей
yours was counted good afternoon
ваш была засчитана добрый день
hello hello i am conducting a
здравствуйте здравствуйте я провожу
sociological study what
социологическое исследование какой в
percentage of idiots in russia please tell me
россии процент идиотов скажите пожалйста
you support  the war in ukraine or not the
вы поддерживаете войну в украине или нет
question is
вопрос
why and to whom is the rag but i am doing
зачем и кому тряпку но я делаю
sociological why your answer is clear
социологические зачем ваш ответ понятен
question
вопрос
i am doing a sociological survey what
я делаю социологический опрос какой в
percentage of idiots in russia please tell me
россии процент идиотов скажите
you will support the war in ukraine
пожалуйста вы поддержите войну в украине
or not let’s simplify the task for us
или нет давайте нам упрощу задачу
just you support the war the clinic
просто вы поддерживаете войну клиника
understood let’s forgive you
понял давайте вам прощу задачу
you want a task just say wait yes here I
хотите просто скажите ждет да вот я
take the checkboxes mark
забираю галочки отмечают
you say you support me fever said
вы скажете вы поддержите меня жар сказал
thank you
спасибо
yes you are watching I am doing a sociological
да вы смотрите я делаю социологический
survey which track and the percentage of idiots
опрос какой трассе и процент идиотов
please tell me you will support the war in
скажите пожалуйста вы поддержите войну в
ukraine or not
украине или нет
question repeat I am conducting a sociological survey  English
вопрос повтори я провожу социологический
poll what is the percentage of idiots in russia
опрос каков в россии процент идиотов
please tell me if you support the
скажите пожалуйста вы поддерживаете
war in ukraine or not well judging by it comes
войну в украине или нет ну судя по идет
from ukraine i will say so no they don’t
из украины я скажу так что нет не
support if you think it’s
поддерживают если считаете что
wrong and that putin sent troops into
неправильно да что путин ввел войска в
ukraine in ukraine because idiots
украину в украине потому что идиоты
ask how we can support ukraine
прошу как можем поддерживать украину
judge idiotic by the
судью идиотскими по сами вещи 20 через
things themselves  what is wrong that
то есть вы считаете что неправильно что
putin's troops in ukraine
путин войска в украину
no they didn't take a
нет не брали
good day
добрый день
to look i am doing a sociological
до посмотрите я делаю социологическое
study
исследование
what is the percentage of idiots in russia please tell
каков в россии процент идиотов скажите
me you support the war in ukraine
пожалйста вы поддержите войну в украине
or not
или нет
do you support the war in ukraine or not
вы поддерживаете войну в украине или нет
ukraine do not
украина вообще не
support the war in ukraine at all do you support
поддерживаю в украине вы поддерживаете
or not what  russia on the floor cry
или нет что россия на полу cry
do you think that putin is wrong  did
вы считаете что путин неправильно сделал
that he attacked ukraine to
что напал на украину на
your question the answer is counted thank you
ваш вопрос ответ засчитан спасибо
please for participating in the survey and
пожалуйста за участие в опросе и
frightening grandfather hello good afternoon because I
пугающий дед здрасьте добрый день ведь я
am doing a sociological survey what
делаю социологический опрос какой
percentage of
процент
you support
вы поддержите
you support it yes everything
вам ее поддерживают поддерживаете да все
already had its own look around good afternoon
уже было свой взгляд вокруг добрый день
and you look I am conducting a sociological survey
а вы смотрите я провожу социологическое
survey what is the percentage of idiots in russia
исследование какое в россии процент
please tell me if you
идиотов скажите пожалуйста вы
support the war in ukraine or not
поддерживаете войну в украине или нет
[music]
[музыка]
will you support the war in
вы подержите войну в украине да
ukraine yes yes your vote is counted
да ваш голос засчитан добрый день добрый
or
войну в украине или нет
not, not only did your frame flash immediately
вот не только кадр ваш мелькнул сразу на
on Zelinsky, you will say, supporting
на зелински вы скажете вы поддерживая
yourself, you raised the issue, hold the
себе отчет поставил вопросе подержите
war in Ukraine, there are no
война в украине нет
Natsiks, you need to remove everything from there, your answer is
нациков надо убрать оттуда все ваш ответ
accepted even for your thought, I remember the
принят дуже дякую за вашу думку помню
day,
день
press the people for work, yes, look, I’m doing a
пресс народ за труд да смотрите я делаю
sociological survey  what is the
социологический опрос какой в россии
percentage of idiots in russia please tell me  do you
процент идиотов скажите пожалуйста вы
support the war in ukraine or not
поддерживаете войну в украине или нет
clothes but now you support there is the
одежду но сейчас поддерживаете есть
current moment connection with the
теперешняя данный момент связи с
actions of the ukrainian troops until we support
действиями украинских войск до подержим
thanks your vote is accepted new day
спасибо ваш голос принят новый день
hello yes look I am conducting a
здравствуйте да вот смотрите я провожу
sociological study what
социологическое исследование какой в
percentage of idiots in russia please tell me
россии процент идиотов скажите
you will support the war in ukraine
пожалуйста вы поддержите войну в украине
or  no
или нет о
matter what you depend on the percentages go while the colors
чём вы зависит проценты идет пока цвета
I collect the answer and then the scientists are already
я собираю ответ а потом ученые уже
sociologists they process and make
социологи они обрабатывают и делают
graphs and diagrams
графики и диаграммы
troops to Ukraine you ask new different questions,
войска в украину новые разные вопросы
but I want to clarify the understanding of
задаете но я хочу уточнить понимание
our war, here is a manual for me.
войны наши меня тут методичке .
well, there
ну-ка методичка там
is a manual there is one question that does not
есть один вопрос не
clarify there are thousands of rivers
уточняющий есть тысячи рек
would float we are clarifying please tell me
бы плавает мы уточняем скажите
Putin is correct and
пожалуйста вот путин правильность и
left the troops I look out
оставил войска выгляну
Putin is correct to do that he sent troops
путин правильно сделать что ввел войска
to Ukraine
в украину
there your answer is accepted thanks good
там-то ваш ответ принят спасибо добрый
afternoon
день
hello
здравствуйте
idiots please tell me
идиотов скажите пожалуйста
you will support the war  in ukraine or there is no
вы поддержите войну в украине или нет
war your answer is accepted
войны ваш ответ принят
good afternoon
добрый день
good afternoon and you look I am conducting a
добрый день а вы смотрите я провожу
study of some kind of heart I saw
исследование какой-то сердца видел
please tell me please you support you
скажите пожалуйста вы поддержите вы
press the
нажмите
war is not a special operation until your answer is
война не то спецоперацию до ваш ответ
accepted compliance
принят соблюдение
you watched I am conducting a sociological
вы смотрели я провожу социологическое
study
исследование
what percentage of idiots in russia tell me
какой в россии процент идиотов скажите
please do you support the war in
пожалйста вы поддерживаете войну в
ukraine or
украине или нет
not that
того что
in every country there is a lot of support for the
в каждой стране много идет поддерживая
war.  then no, that is, it’s still
войну . то нет то есть высчитать еще
wrong to calculate even in the measurement, I’ll hold it wrong, I’ll give it
неправильно даже в измерении я подержу
wrong, they led the troops to Ukraine,
неправильно дашу вели войска в украину
you correctly support that here are the troops and
правильно поддерживаете что вот войск и
supporting against the war, then the fact that your
поддерживая против войны то то что ваши
Russian troops entered Ukraine,
войска российские вы вошли в украину в
you support it,
это вы поддерживаете на
I support what is possible in our
я поддерживаю то что в наш правительству
government  burn all your answer accepted good
можно сжечь всю вашу ответ принят добрый
afternoon good afternoon, but look, I
день добрый день а вот смотрите я
am conducting a sociological study from
провожу социологическое исследование с
which Russia the percentage of idiots please tell me
какого россии процент идиотов скажите
if you support the war in Ukraine
пожалуйста вы поддержите войну в украине
or not,
или нет
if someone says it supports,
считают если кто говорит поддерживает
then I’m an idiot, I’m just in front of and further material is
значит идиот я только перед и материала
already calculated by sociologists and is not
дальше социологи уже там вычисляет и не
given  it’s just
дается просто
that I don’t have one, I’m ambiguous, because,
у меня не одна у меня неоднозначный так
well, let’s say on this score,
как а ну скажем на этот счет
I don’t support any warriors at all
я вообще вы воины не поддерживаю никакие
if you think that our
от если считаете что неправильно наши
Russia attacked our eyes wrong, no, I
россия напала на зрения нет я по-другому
generally understand a completely different approach in a different way,
вообще понимаете совсем другой подход у
I have a sense, let
меня есть смысл давайте
me how  in childhood,
я как в детстве вот
if they throw a cry for our beat, then
если клич бросают наших бьют то
you can’t give it and
придавать нельзя и
we all went there and are happy and
все мы шли туда и рад и разбирались
I also figured out that I think that Russia is not
также считаю что и россия она не
treacherous, they don’t attach their own,
предательское не придают своих
you support it, but the prints on our
вы поддерживаю так а принты на нашем
youtube channel go, then it goes and
youtube-канале идет-то оно идет и
protects them, so you support it, so it
защищают их значит поддерживаете так что
means it supports you see correctly
значит поддерживает вы видите правильно
that Russia is going to beat someone in Ukraine to
что россия идёт бить в украину кого-то
defend it like that
защищать так у
who has to defend yours, that is,
кого защищать своих то есть
support to calculate eat it
поддерживайте высчитать ешь это
correctly,
правильно
but you think that it’s more correct
но вы считаете что пред правильнее
to give it literal, it’s used I
придать буквальным , используется не
don’t want your thoughts habitually quieter
хочу ваших мыслей привычной тише
correctly yes on the highway and
правильно да по трассе и делает
does not attach your own correctly of course
что не придает своих правильно конечно
your voice is protective thanks good afternoon
ваш голос защитным спасибо добрый день
good
добрый
protection operation
операцию по защите
I want  say zero percent in russia
хочу сказать в россии ноль процентов
we support russia we support
мы поддерживаем россию мы поддерживаем
special operations I will take you
спецоперации у вас отвезу
I do cooperate I have such a cable in
я делаю сотрудничать я трос такой в
russia of civil idiots and
россии гражданских идиотов и
support
поддержки
supports the
поддерживает
war in ukraine supported
войну в украине поддерживали
good afternoon
добрый день
drew
нарисовал
I don’t look I conduct sociological
я не смотрите я провожу социологические
research
исследования
percent of idiots please tell me how
процент идиотов скажите пожалуйста как
you feel about her
вы относитесь к ней
ukraine slippery wa  from the Polish eagle to
украина скользкий вас польский орел на
tattoos in from Poland I understood to
татуировки в из польши понял
use
использовать
our fraternal Slavic people of Poland,
наш братский славянский народ польский
I will not also return to chase into the fields and fields
не тоже вернусь на погоня в поля и поля
and fields are scorched, you can see here the Polish coat of arms
и поля палят видно тут герб польские у
you lived there white
вас там жил белый
I immediately look to catch your face
я сразу смотрю поймать вас лицо ли соков
intellectually like a Pole no
интеллектуально как у поляка никакой
where  you are sitting where you are now
где вы сейчас сидите где вы находитесь
I am conducting such a sociological
я провожу такое социологическое
study in russia the percentage of idiots
исследование в россии процент идиотов
please tell me you will support the war in
скажите пожалуйста вы поддержите войну в
ukraine or not
украине или нет
it is as they
это как гласит я собираю данные потом
say  Look, I’m a person who
аргументировать смотрите я за человек
supports what kills people in
поддерживает то что убивает людей в
Ukraine, for example, yesterday,
украине вот например денницы вчера
how many people were killed by a rocket there
сколько там людей убили так ракетой там
in Kremenchug in Mariupol in Kharkov in Kiev,
в кременчуге в мариуполе в харькове в
yes, these people are idiots, the thought is not to
киеве так-то да это люди идиоты мысли не
support the killing of people, that is, I
поддерживать убийство людей то есть я
understood you correctly that you  here you
правильно вас понял что вы здесь
communicate precisely whether it is pure, that is, we are not
общаетесь именно чисто ли то есть нам не
interested at all, not at any
интересно вообще не на какой-нибудь
simple people  just common
просто людскую человеческом просто общей
if we are at war and your country is
если у нас идет война и ваша страна
killing our people what is
убивает наших людей какой
it worth I will
стоит я буду
believe that this is the most wildly remember and
полагают что этим самым дико помнишь а
I want you want to talk about michael
хочу вы хотите поговорить о майкле
jackson madonna about football you come
джексоне мадонне о футболе вы приходите
on
на
youtube we know if they are not
ютубчике нам известны если их не будет
let's try look look  what topics
давайте попробуем вот гляди какие темы о
do I understand what topics do you
чем-то занимаюсь понимать какие темы вы
want to talk about guria give me everything of
хотите поговорить гурию дай мне обо всем
course in many respects
конечно во многом
let's say the passage of corrugation
допустим проходе гофрирования
programmers let's talk about
программисты давайте давайте поговорим о
for example
например
let's talk about children let's talk about
давайте о детях поговорим
rockets yesterday in the winery
вчера в виннице ракеты убила
let's say another topic let's talk
давайте скажите другую тему поговорим
about another topic
про другую тему
you say  topic topic I’m your topic in the course
вы скажете тему тему я вашу тему в ходе
to that understanding if but we have common
к тому пониманию если но у нас общие
topics and
темы и
immediately
сразу
came here select I want you about -
сюда пришли выберите хочу ты про -
just another other load I don’t know if
просто другой другой груз я не знаю
they study at school, they study only, but because
они учатся всего ли но из за того что у
we have a war now children  study
нас война сейчас дети учатся
remotely because Russian bastards are
дистанционно потому что русский [__]
bombing schools
бомбят школы
[music]
[музыка]
general education for some other
общем образования на какие-то другие
sections
секции
goes to  drawing goes around, but because
уходит на рисование ходит но из-за того
the Russian bastard bombs our
что русский [__] их бомбят наши
cities during air raids, am
города во время воздушных тревог am
must run away from the bomb shelter instead of
должны убегать бомбоубежище вместо того
doing drawing, some
чтобы заниматься рисовали некоторые не
cannot let the children go, the
могут отпустить детей
bomb must also run away, because a
тоже надо убегать бомбе потому что в дом
rocket also hits the house 300 places in Ukraine, well,
попадает тоже ракета 300 мест украины ну
from Ukraine with  a low start
с украины с низкого старта
and diodes here
и диодов тут
for eight years the
протяжении восьми лет
father of
отец
people of people will become it is very
людей людей станет это это очень
sad that pro-Russian bastards have been
печально что пророссийские [__]
killing Ukrainian people for 8 years in Donetsk
убивали 8 лет украинских людей в донецке
Donetsk this is Ukraine people who are children
донецк это украина люди которые дети
who died in Donetsk in Luhansk this is
которые погибли в донецке в луганске это
our Ukrainian all citizens of
наши украинские все граждане
Russian bastards at the beginning you are
русских [__] начале вы
such a Russian there  the militants captured
такого там российские боевики захватили
we will return for 8 years how it all started in the
вернемся на 8 лет с чего началось все на
Donbas well tell me the
донбассе ну расскажи мне
policy has changed they
политика поменялась они
didn’t want to they wanted
не захотели они хотели
from what day the war in the Donbass started
с какого дня началась война на донбассе
and
а
[music]
[музыка]
what month the day
какой месяц день
I’ll tell you for sure see April 12
я вам точно скажу смотрите 12 апреля
people although you yourself will need
людям хотя сам программиста будете надо
to deal with the programmer  programming
заниматься программированием компьютеров
some computers according to the system I program people  she
каких-то по системе программирую людей
gave me a psychologist and they gave me a
мне психолог и
psychologist about his whole first
приложили психолог о его целого первый
example when a person starts swearing
пример когда человек начинать матюкаться
so it means he is already burning
так это значит у него уже подгорает
up he is burning up
у него подгорает
hey
эй
kid I don’t
пацанчик не убегаю
run away
у
good afternoon to death I did a
добрый день до смерти я делал
sociological survey what
социологический опрос какого в россии
percentage of idiots in Russia please tell me you
процент идиотов скажите пожалуйста вы
support the war boucle not  or not who
поддерживаете войну букле не или нет кто
percentage
процент
[music]
[музыка]